kiwi.qa 2016-01-13

# Privacy Policy - Kiwi

Welcome to a web site (the “Site”) of Chatous, Inc. (“Chatous”, "Kiwi", “we,” “us” and/or “our”). This Site is operated by Chatous and has been created to provide information about our company and our social Q&A platform, mobile applications and related services (together with the Site, the “Services”) to our Service visitors (“you”, “your”). Chatous is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of information collected from visitors to the Site and Services, including personally identifiable data (“Personal Data”). By using Kiwi, you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**1\. Information We Collect**

When you interact with us through the Services, Kiwi may collect Personal Data and other information from you, as further described below:

**Personal Data That You Provide Through the Services:**

We collect Personal Data from you when you voluntarily provide such information, for example when you register with us, engage in a chat, add information to your profile, or if you send us an email. Wherever Kiwi collects Personal Data we make an effort to provide a link to this Privacy Policy. 

**If you choose to provide such information, you are giving Kiwi permission to use and store that information consistent with this policy. If you provide Personal Data to the Services, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of Kiwi and the authorized third parties referred to herein located in the United States.**

**Location Information:** Our Service may collect and use your location information (for example, by using the IP address on your computer or the GPS on your mobile device) to provide certain functionality of our Service. If you choose to enable our location features, your location information may be publicly displayed within the Service. Please keep in mind that other users can see this information about you, and they may use it or disclose it to other individuals or entities outside of our control and without your knowledge. Your location information may be subject to abuse, misuse, and monitoring by others, so please be careful if you choose to enable location functionality. We may also use your location information in an aggregate way, as described above in the “Aggregated Data” section.

Kiwi uses the Google Places API(s) for location searches and as a result is using the Google Maps/Google Earth API(s). Pursuant to the Google Maps/Google Earth APIs Terms of Service, use of this location feature is also subject to the Google privacy policy, which can be found at <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>, and is incorporated with this reference.

**User Data:** In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Services, Kiwi often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and Kiwi may share this aggregate data with its affiliates, agents and business partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. Kiwi may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

**Aggregated Data:** In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Services, Kiwi often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and Kiwi may share this aggregate data with its affiliates, agents and business partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. Kiwi may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

**Non-Identifiable Data:** When you interact with Kiwi through the Services, we receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information such as Internet Protocol address (“IP Address”), a unique user ID, the content and pages that you access on Kiwi and the dates and times that you visit the Site. In addition, if you come to the Site via a link from another site, we may also track the source of that link. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. Kiwi may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by Kiwi affiliates, agents or service providers. The Services may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, and the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers. It is important to note that no Personal Data is available or used in this process.

**Information Regarding “Cookies”:** Like many other websites, Kiwi may send one or more cookies – small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters – to your computer. We use cookies to improve our Site and make it easier to use. Cookies permit us to recognize users and avoid repetitive requests for the same information. Kiwi may use cookies to track user traffic patterns as described above. Kiwi may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Kiwi. Persistent cookies can be removed. In all cases in which we use cookies, we will not collect Personal Data except with your permission. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser, however, some features on the Kiwi may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. Please review your web browser “Help” file to modify your cookie settings. 

**2\. Information From Other Sources**

We may collect information about you from other sources, including from partners, and from commercially available sources (such as data aggregators and public databases). The following are examples of information we may collect from other sources:

Data you authorize us to access through your use of Facebook Connect. In general, the types and amount of Personal Data we collect vary depending on the activity. Kiwi endeavors to limit the collection of Personal Data to information we believe is minimally necessary to achieve our stated collection purposes.

**3\. Our Use of Your Personal Data and Other Information**

Kiwi uses the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by email, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to the Services, we will use your Personal Data to provide you with access to such services and to monitor your use of such services. Kiwi and its subsidiaries and affiliates (the “Related Companies”) may also use your Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information collected through the Services to help us operate, maintain, enhance, and deliver the various features and services found on the Site; as well as to track user-generated content and users to comply as a service provider with the DMCA and other applicable laws. Kiwi uses all of the Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information that we collect from users to understand and analyze the usage trends and preferences of our users, to improve the way the Site works and looks, and to create new features and functionality. Further, Kiwi may use Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information to: (a) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit Kiwi; (b) monitor your participation in various sections of the Kiwi; (c) customize our service to you, including by providing you with recommendations and (c) monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed. We may use your e-mail address for administrative communications such as notifying you of major Kiwi updates, for customer service purposes, and to send privacy or security-related notices.

If Kiwi intends on using any Personal Data in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the Personal Data is collected.

**4\. Disclosure of Information**

Kiwi is not in the business of selling your information. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you. We may share your Personal Data with companies that provide services to us, including outside vendors, contractors, or agents who help us manage our business activities. Such entities only use your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and for no other purpose than to provide us with necessary services. Kiwi may disclose Personal Data if required to do so by law or under the good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (including, without limitation, U.S. copyright or trademark laws) or respond to a court order, subpoena, judicial or other governmental requirement or warrant in a manner required by the requesting entity. Kiwi also reserves the right to disclose Personal Data that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; enforce our Terms of Service; protect Kiwi from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to initiate, render, bill and collect for amounts owed to Kiwi; to investigate and defend ourselves against third-party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the Site; or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Kiwi, our Users, or others. As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets. Kiwi may also share your Personal Data with our Related Companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

**Special Note about Profile Information:** Kiwi is all about sharing questions and answers, enabling people to ask questions, and building friendships. To that end, before starting to use Kiwi, you can optionally provide Personal Data and other information, such as your name, photo, age, gender, and location (as discussed above). By doing so, you understand and acknowledge that this information may be shared with other users on the Service.

**Special Note about Questions and Answers:** When you engage with other another user of the Service through a question or answer, any information or content you choose to provide in that exchange may be provided to such other user. Please note that conversations on the site are screened by an automated system for spam and select messages may be read by a human being in order to improve Kiwi' anti-spam software or for other quality control purposes.

**5\. Your Choices**

You can visit the Site without providing any Personal Data. If you choose not to provide any Personal Data, you may not be able to use certain Services. 

**6\. Exclusions**

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by Kiwi other than Personal Data collected through the Services. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to Kiwi through the Services or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Services, such as forums, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Kiwi shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.

**7\. Children**

Kiwi does not knowingly collect or retain Personal Data about persons under 13 years of age. Any person who provides their Personal Data to Kiwi through the Services represents that they are 13 years of age or older. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Data on the Services without their permission. If Kiwi learns that Personal Data of persons under the age of 13 years has been collected on the Site without verifiable parental consent, then Kiwi will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

**8\. Data Security**

Kiwi takes reasonable measures to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. However, no data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We cannot, therefore, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Kiwi, and you do so at your own risk. Please know that although we make our best efforts to keep your information secure, this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

**9\. International Visitors**

The Site is hosted in the United States. If you visit Kiwi from the European Union or other regions of the world with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from laws of the United States, then please understand that you are transferring your Personal Data outside of those jurisdictions to the United States for the uses identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy. By providing your Personal Data to Kiwi you consent to that transfer.

**10\. Third Parties**

Except as expressly provided otherwise, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information that Kiwi collects from you or that you disclose to us. If you disclose your information to others besides Kiwi different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Kiwi does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

**11\. Other Terms and Conditions**

Your access to and use of the Services is subject to the Terms of Service at [www.kiwi.qa/terms](https://www.kiwi.qa/terms)

**12\. Updates to this Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this Policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the "Last Revision" date below and will post the updated Policy on this page. Your continued use of the Services after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

**13\. Contact**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at team@Kiwi.qa

**14\. Last Revision Date**

This policy was last revised on February 6, 2015.
